Hello friends, my name is Ashwini Kumar.
Friends, as you all know, I am
already selected in ICICI Bank here.
Today's
topic of the video here is going to be
friends, if
you already know about the bank's program, then friends, you must already
know that the ICICI program here, the
Aspire Bank
program, in this, friends, the job that is given to you here,
you are directly given a
job in ICICI Bank and that
too friends, on a very good pay
package here and brother, it is very good on
your position here, that is,
you get a grade of D1 here, in this
position, if brother,
through this program here, you get
selected in ICICI Bank here.
In this, friends,
by completing two simple steps here, you
can easily get a job directly in ICICI Bank, friends, on roll job here.  Like
friends, here your first step is that in this,
in the first step, your assessment
test is cleared here.  After that
friends, your interview takes place here.
After that friends, your offer letter
arrives.  After receiving the offer letter, you have to
go to Neem Rana here.
Friends, in today's video, you will get
complete information about this Aspire Bank program here
in today's video.
And brother, many people are
facing a problem here.
Like I will show you on the screen
here that their
assessment test is not getting completed
or they are getting some error etc.
like they are getting error in the photo etc. So
friends, I am going to tell
you here in today's video how to fix this error here
because brother, I have received a
lot of DMs etc., a lot of
messages etc. that the
assessment test that we have here is not able to proceed from here.
So friends, please watch this video till the
end.  You will
understand it here.  Friends, in today's video,
we are going to give complete information
here in today's video.  Step
by step how you have to apply here
and brother, is there going to be a program of Aspire Bank.
For this, friends,
you have to do only one thing.  If you like the video, please give it
a like.  If you are new to the channel then
friends, you have to subscribe to the channel
because friends,
you keep getting such content here.  Without
wasting any time let's start the video.
Friends, before we start the video, let me
tell you one thing.
Friends, here we have hiring directly in HDFC Bank.
Friends, the salary
here is going to be from ₹29,000 to
₹34,000.
If you are interested brother, then
write HDFC Bank here below and brother, write
your locations
here below in the comment box.
Rest of the friends, let's start the video here.
So friends, in today's
video we are going to talk about the
program of Aspire Bank.  As
you friends, you might already know
that ICICI Bank has
launched a course here,
Aspire Bank program, in which you are
given the opportunity to work directly in ICICI Bank.  Friends, in this you have
some criteria like
your age should be below 25 years.
Secondly, friends, the
criteria for this is going to be that in
your
qualification here, friends, in your
graduation and 10th and 12th,
friends, you should have 60% marks in all three.
After that friends, you become
eligible here.  Friends, if you have
both these three things then
brother, after that you apply here.
After applying, friends,
you get the link for the assessment test.
After that friends, you have to
clear the assessment test here.
Friends, after clearing the assessment test, you are directly
interviewed face to face here.  As soon as you
complete everything here like intro etc.,
then friends, you have to
go to NIT here.  Which
friends, you will get here in Alwar, Rajasthan.
NIT friends,
you have to go here.
Its training is done here for 2 months.
Friends, even within 2 months,
you are given a stipend of ₹1-18,000 here.
After that friends,
you get an honorarium job here.  That means,
after completion of your training here after 2 months, you
get the final job here.  After that,
friends, the salary package that you are going to have is
from ₹4.5.5 lakh, brother, your
package goes up to ₹5.5 lakh here, friends.
Friends, here it will depend on
your location where
you are living.  For example, friends, if you
consider Delhi here, then
friends, in all the metro
cities, you can
get a little higher package here.   That
means you are given a package here up to ₹5.5 lakh.
Now friends, many
people here are facing a problem.
As I told you here in the beginning of the video.
Like
I will show it to you here on the screen also.
One problem that is
arising here is that after clearing the assessment, your photo etc. will be displayed here
as if
you are going to give the assessment here.
Before that you have to upload the photo here.  There is a
problem here.  It is
written above that your case is
not being processed here.  So
friends, for that let me tell you that ICICI
Bank has
given a new update here.  In which friends,
what do you have to do here?  As soon as you
take a selfie here, friends,
you get an error.  You have to take a selfie
and brother, you have to say here that
my name is this.  L'm from.  I have done my
graduation from here.  You have to
speak a little so that your voice here can
detect you.
Whatever you
say here through your microphone, your voice should be deducted.
What do you have to
say here in this manner?  After that, friends,
your selfie will be
uploaded here easily.
What are you doing here that you don't speak?  You
take a selfie and brother, what happens there is
that it does not get uploaded.  So
brother, you can fix this error here.
Friends, the error is coming to
you because what do you have to do here
?  You have to take your selfie here
and brother, you have to speak a little here,
tell something about yourself and it will
deduct your voice here and brother, the
process will start here.  After that,
brother, you can continue the assessment test here
and brother, as soon as the
assessment test is cleared,
then friends,
you go to the interview phase here.  If
friends, you need my help or
you are not able to clear your assessment here
or you are
not able to clear the interview,
you are scared of what all will be
asked there, what will happen, what will not happen, then brother
friends, I have its proper session here, friends, I can
help you with the test here and brother friends, whatever
your intro is, brother, I can
help you 100% in that too,
if brother, you need help, then
brother, the link of the WhatsApp group is given below,
friends, go and
join the WhatsApp group here.  Please send me a
personal message.  You will get my number
here, that brother of the admin, please
message me personally.
Friends, details will be shared with you here as to
how
you
can easily clear its assessment test here and friends, you
can easily clear its interview here and
friends, you can directly get a job here.
Friends, I have already
helped 10 to 15 people here so far.
Those who have cleared the assessment test here.
Those friends who have
cleared the interview here.  And brother,
offer letters of some people have also arrived.  If you want to
see me brother, I will come here.  Brother, if
you want to see the proof etc. here then brother,
you will find the link of the WhatsApp group below.  Please send me a
message that brother,
you want to see the proof.  Brother, I
can also share the proof with you here.   The
rest is up to you friends.  If
friends, you are not able to clear the appointment test
or you are
not able to clear the intro.  ICICI Bank which
is a program of Asi Bank, friends, you do
not have the program of Aspire Bank here or
friends, you have some other program like
PO program or Axis's Young
Program or Kotak's Next Jain
Program, any one of them can be there.  There
is no problem.  We have the solution.
You can connect with us
and brother, we
are absolutely ready to help you here.  Friends, we will get you
selected here as
long as you remain connected with us.
Rest of the friends, the
main topic of today's video here was that the
program of Aspire Bank is
going on here right now.  Brother, it is open now.  Those
friends who have not applied yet, you should quickly go and apply.
Rest of the friends, the
process is going on very fast here.
If you apply for this, you
complete its eligibility criteria here.
So friends, your process is happening very quickly here
and you
can also get selected here very soon.  So friends, I have
told you here in today's video.
I hope you liked this information very much.  If you like the
video then please like it.
Friends, if you have
not yet subscribed to this channel, then brother, go
quickly and subscribe to this channel.
See you in the next video.
Take care of me.  Bye